Honey？
宝贝
- Have you seen my checkbook？- Yeah。It's downstairs in the living room.
- 我的支票簿放哪了 - 在楼下客厅
Darling，are you okay？
亲爱的 你没事吧
Fine！
没事
Are you sure？
你确定吗
I'm just gonna take the dog for a walk.
我出门遛一下狗
Okay.
好
Nice office.
办公室真漂亮
Nice family.
合家欢乐啊
Sorry to disturb you at this time of night…
这么晚打扰您真是抱歉
but we have a little problem.
不过… 有个小问题
Your boss owes me money.
你老板欠我钱
A lot of money.
一大笔钱
And I'm here to collect it.
我是来取钱的
I'm just the accountant。I don't know anything.
我只是个会计 我什么都不知道
You don't need to know anything…
你不需要知道什么
except the combination to the safe.
只要知道保险柜的密码就行了
You do know the combination，yes？
这你总该知道吧
Yes.
知… 知道
Perfect。Please.
很好 有劳了
Get in.
进去
This is 310-555-0199。Leave a message.
本机号码310-5550199 请留言
Hello，my friend。It's Malankov.
老朋友你好 我是曼伦科夫
I came to your office to collect my money.
我来你办公室取钱
What a disappointment to see it's not here.
结果竹篮打水一场空
But I am leaving you something here in return.
不过我会给你留份回礼
As a reminder.
让你长长记性
I cannot wait any longer.
我的耐心要耗尽了
My best to the family.
代我向您家人问好
《飓风营救3》
（生日快乐）
Sweet.
真可爱
Yeah.
是啊
How old？
多大了
No matter how old they are，my friend，they will always be our baby.
不管他们长到多大 总是我们的宝贝孩子
Ain't that true？Come on，big guy.
说得太对了 来吧 大家伙
Thank you.
谢谢
（已怀孕）
- Whoa！- Happy birthday！
- 哇 - 生日快乐
Dad！
爸爸
- My birthday's not even for three days。- You're always saying I'm so predictable.
- 离我生日还有三天呢 - 你总是说我循规蹈矩
I wanted to shake things up a bit，make it a little less predictable.
所以我想改变一下 不那么墨守成规了
Sorry.
对不起
Come in.
快进来
- Champagne glasses？- You know me.
- 高脚杯在哪 - 你又不是不了解我
Why would I have champagne glasses？
我哪来的高脚杯
Or a giant stuffed panda？
或者一个巨大的毛绒熊猫
I heard that.
我听到了
- Inappropriate？- Well，I mean…
- 不太礼貌啊 - 我是说…
- not if I was 7。- I can return it…
- 我早就不是七岁了 - 我可以把它还回去
or you can hang on to it until you have a 7-year-old of your own.
要么先放你这 等你自己的孩子七岁大的时候
Not funny.
一点也不好笑
- Hey，baby。Babe？- Hey！
- 嗨 宝贝 - 嗨
- Hey，look who's here。- Mr。Mills.
- 看看谁来了 - 米尔斯先生
Hello，Jimy.
你好 吉米
- How are you？- Good。You？
- 你还好吧 - 挺好的 你呢
You know。Hey.
就那样呗 嗨
Hi.
嗨
Hey，if you guys are having a father- daughter moment，I can really…
那个 要是你们父女俩想独处的话 我就…
No，no，no。I just dropped by。I thought I'd do something unpredictable.
不 不 我只是路过进来看看 想要… 打破成规
Kim's always pointing out how predictable I am.
金姆总是说我太循规蹈矩了
That's funny coming from her。You wanna talk about predictable？
这可真有意思 你居然还好意思说别人循规蹈矩
- I'm not predictable！- Oh，come on.
- 我才不循规蹈矩呢 - 得了吧
Every single day she goes to the same exact store，
每天她都去同一家商店
right off campus，every morning before class…
离学校不远 每天早上上学前
- and gets the same peach yogurt drink。- Stop.
- 买杯一模一样的桃子酸奶 对吧 - 别说了
The fourth one from the back。Not the fifth one，not the third one.
从后面数第四个不是第五 也不是第三 对吧
The fourth one will stay cold，but not too cold.
因为第四个冰得恰到好处
That way，when she's drinking it，as a snack in between classes…
这么一来 等她课间休息喝的时候 它还是…
It's still cold.
还是… 很冰的
I know。I would do exactly the same thing.
我知道 我也会干一样的事情
Yeah，the OCD gene.
是啊 强迫症遗传
What's with the bubbly？
这香槟是干嘛的
Pre-birthday celebration.
预先庆祝一下生日
If you don't mind，I just think it's a little early to pop open a bottle.
爸你要是不介意 我是觉得现在喝酒早了点
Yeah，no problem.
也是 没问题
I'll put it in the fridge.
我把它放冰箱里
What's that？
你怎么了
Whoa。A panda.
干得好
That was awesome.
刚刚真是…
I'll leave you two.
那我就留你俩二人世界吧
Dad，don't…
老爸别…
You don't have to take it。Now I feel bad.
别拿走 这下我心里不好受了
Yeah，you should feel bad.
嗯 你是该不好受
I'll exchange it for something more predictable.
我去换个更循规蹈矩的礼物来
- Love you。- Take it easy，Jimy.
- 爱你 - 吉米保重
Bye.
好嘞
Hey，babe.
嗨 宝贝
- Is something wrong？- Nothing.
- 出什么事了吗 - 没什么
Are you sure，babe？
真的吗 宝贝
Stop。Stop.
停下 别这样
I just need a second，okay？
我想静一静 好吗
（我爱你 爸爸）
You might want to buckle up，Phillip.
你最好系好安全带 菲利普
Bryan.
我是布莱恩
How did it go？
怎么样
Great。Fantastic.
挺好的 好极了
Couldn't have gone better.
好得不能再好
The panda was not a hit，I take it.
我猜熊猫不太吃香啊
Careful what you say。He's sitting right next to me.
别瞎说 人家正坐我旁边呢
When did she grow up，Lenore？
她是什么时候长大的 丽诺尔
I know。It goes so fast。All of it.
我懂 时间过得太快 所有事都是
Where are you？
你在哪呢
Just going home。Make a little dinner.
正要回家 做点晚餐
- If you'd like to join us。- 「Us」？
- 想不想跟我们一起 - 我们
Me and the panda.
我和熊猫
I'll… take a rain check on that.
我… 要不还是下次再说吧
If that's okay with you？
你答应吗
And the panda？
还有熊猫
That's fine by us.
我们都答应了
I'll see you.
回头见
See you.
拜拜
I know what you're thinking.
我知道你想什么呢
Keep it to yourself.
别说出来
- Hey。- Lennie.
- 嗨 - 莉妮
You changed your mind！
你改变主意了
Yeah。You left the door open.
嗯 你的门虚掩着
Come on in.
快进来
Okay.
好的
- I'm not intruding？- No，of course you're not.
- 我没有太冒昧吧… - 当然没有
I was just preparing dinner。Drink？
我正准备晚餐呢 来一杯
Yes，please.
好的
Thanks for coming over.
谢谢你能过来
Cheers.
干杯
- You look stressed。- Yeah.
- 你看起来有点焦虑 - 嗯
What？
怎么了
Stuart and I…
我和斯图尔特…
We've tried everything.
我们什么都试过了
Therapy。Counseling。Together，separately.
心理治疗 咨询 无论是两个人一起还是单独去
He wants it to work。He really does.
他是真心想挽回
And you？
那你呢
I know I'm hurting him.
我知道我在伤害他
I just don't feel anything anymore.
我只是什么都感觉不到了
I hate that。I hate not feeling.
我讨厌这种麻木的感觉
I hate going through the motions.
我讨厌走过场的生活
The only thing I feel is trapped.
我唯一感受到的就是被困住了
I have the worst taste in men！
我对男人的品味差劲透顶了
Thanks.
多谢夸奖
No，not you.
我没在说你
Oh，God，I'm sorry.
天啊 真对不起 对不起
It's okay.
没关系
Do you know what I fantasize about？
你知道我幻想什么吗
I'm afraid to ask.
我不敢问
Us.
我们俩
Yeah？
是吗
And right after…
紧接着
the guilt comes roaring in and I feel like such a shit.
罪恶感就淹没了我 让我感觉自己真不是东西
Does it make me a bad person…
这是不是说明我是个坏人
being married to one man，fantasizing about another？
吃着碗里的 看着锅里的
Confused maybe。Bad？No.
你很迷茫 但不是坏人
You must think I'm crazy.
你一定觉得我疯了
If you are，Lennie，you're not the only one.
莉妮 如果连你都疯了 你肯定不是唯一一个
Oh，Lennie.
莉妮
- I'm sorry。- No.
- 对不起 - 没事
It's me that should be apologizing.
该道歉的是我
It's not that I don't want to。Believe me.
不是我不想 但… 相信我
But until you and Stuart clear up your situation…
但在你和斯图尔特撇清关系之前
I think it would do more harm than good.
我觉得这样做弊大于利
For all of us.
对每个人都是如此
Why do you have to be so damn honorable？
你现在装什么清高
Believe me，right now，I wish I weren't.
相信我 我也希望我能放下架子
- I'm gonna go。- Wait.
- 我… 我得走了 - 等等
Here.
给你
I'm going out of town in a couple of days for a month on a job.
我要出趟差 一个月的时间
If you ever feel you need to go someplace just to be by yourself…
如果你想独自去个清净的地方
use it.
别客气
Thank you.
谢谢你
- I put on six pounds of muscle。- Oh，you guys are giving me a hard time.
- 你增肌了六磅 - 你们太会欺负我了
Well，it's not helping your stroke.
肌肉可提高不了你的挥杆准度
You were plus two on the last one.
上个洞你多用了两杆
You？Me？
你 还是我
Did the rest of you get on the green？
你们其他人来吧
But seriously，it's money。It would be fun.
但说真的 有钱拿 有意思
I know。I can't go，Sam.
我知道 我去不成 萨姆
It's a four-man job。We can't do it without you.
这是四个人的活计 没有你我们办不成
I know。But a couple of things have come up…
我知道 我知道 但手头来了几件事
and I'm not comfortable being away for a month right now.
这一个月一时走不开
- Man，you gotta let this go。- You do.
- 老兄 你得放开了 - 没错
Lenore's a grown woman。She can take care of herself.
丽诺尔是个成年人 她能照顾好自己
You're not her husband any longer.
你不再是她丈夫了
But she is my friend.
但她是我朋友
I think you better talk to somebody about this.
我觉得你最好找个人谈谈心
A shrink，maybe.
心理咨询
Why would I go to a shrink when I got you guys？
有你们几个我还要什么心理咨询
There's a good point.
此言倒是不假
Can somebody drop the flag stick？
来个人取下旗杆好吗
Hey，Kim。What's up？
嗨 金姆 什么事
- You want me to take it out？- If you wouldn't mind.
- 要我帮你拿出来 - 如果你不介意的话
Sure。When？
没问题 什么时候
Okay，baby.
好啊 宝贝
Okay。The big moment.
关键一球
That's a good shot.
还不错…
This is an unexpected treat.
真是难得的款待
Yeah，I… need some advice.
我 呃… 需要您的建议
Okay，shoot.
说吧
I guess it's not something I was really planning on…
这大概是我之前根本没有计划过
or even thought about，ever.
甚至想都没有想过的… 从来没有
Anyway，I just wanted your advice.
无论如何 我想听听您的建议
I'm flattered.
受宠若惊啊
- I'm so sorry。Just stop this。- Wow.
- 真不好意思 别闹了 - 哇
Poor lady.
可怜的姑娘
That is going to be serious trouble in a few years。You mark my words.
你别不信 那小鬼过几年就是个大麻烦啊
What was it you wanted to ask？
你想问什么来着
A puppy.
小狗
- A puppy？- Yeah.
- 小狗 - 嗯
I was thinking about getting a puppy.
我在想要不要养条小狗
From where？
哪儿来的
My friend found one behind her building…
我朋友在大楼后面找到一只
and we were trying to find it a home…
我们想给它找个家
we put it on Facebook，
我们把信息挂在脸书上
but nobody claimed it yet，so…
但没人来认领 所以…
You wanna know what I think？
想知道我怎么想吗
Yeah.
嗯
I mean，it's a lot of work.
我觉得这意味着很大的工作量
It's a lot of responsibility.
很重的一份责任
With your lifestyle the way it is at the moment，with college.
相比你的生活方式 而且你还在上学
With a puppy you have to be there
你一直得待在小狗身边
all the time and feed it，walk it.
喂它 遛它 这跟…
It's no different than having a kid.
养个孩子没什么区别
Have you had a chance to look at the menus？
你们看过菜单了吗
Not yet，Annie.
还没呢 安妮
What will I have？
我看看要什么
- Stuart。- Hey，Bryan.
- 斯图尔特 - 嗨 布莱恩
What are you doing here？
你来这干什么
Everything all right？
都还好吧
Yeah。It's fine.
嗯 挺好的
Can I talk to you inside？
方便进来说话吗
Yeah，yeah，sure。I was just making some coffee.
嗯 没问题 我正在煮咖啡
Milk？Sugar？
要加奶加糖吗
Both，please.
呃 都要吧
Okay。Milk，cold or hot？
好的 奶要冷的热的
Hot，please.
呃… 热的
- So，how's business？- Oh，you know.
- 生意怎么样 - 你知道的
Some days good，some days great.
有时候还不错 有时候非常不错
Yeah.
嗯
One sugar or two？
要一块糖 还是两块
Two，please.
两块吧
- Here we go。- Thanks.
- 给你 - 谢谢
I'm sorry to bother you this late…
很抱歉这么晚还来打扰你
but I thought it was more，respectful…
但我觉得这样更…
to say what I have to say to you
能体现我对你谈话的尊重
face-to-face，man-to-man.
比如面对面 一对一这样
So to speak.
听着
I know that Lenore has…
我知道丽诺尔
She's spoken to you about the problems that we've been having.
跟你讲过我们之间的问题你是个好人
You're a good guy，Bryan。I like you.
布莱恩 我挺喜欢你的
You're a respectful guy.
你是个值得尊敬的人
And，listen，I'm not accusing you of anything.
听我说 我没有任何责怪你的意思
But Lenore and I… if our marriage is gonna work…
但是… 如果要想挽回我和丽诺尔的婚姻
that can't happen with you in between us.
你夹在我们当中肯定是不行的
But，Stuart…
斯图尔特
there's nothing between Lenore and I，other than we share Kim.
我和丽诺尔之间除了金姆之外 一清二白
I didn't say there was.
我没说你们不清白
Obviously…
明显
you share a daughter…
这是你们共同的女儿
and… you've tried to be the best father that you can，
你也努力试着做一个好父亲
under the circumstances.
至少在某些情况下
And… part of that means the two of you talking and staying in touch.
而这意味着你们俩之间会交流 联系
But I still want you to stop seeing my wife.
但我还是希望你能别再见我的妻子
Until we sort things out.
直到我们之间的问题解决为止
Does she know you're here？
她知道你来我这吗
It doesn't matter if she does，or if she doesn't。That's not the point.
她知不知道不重要 这不是重点
I'm asking you to stop seeing my wife。Can you do that？
我在要求你以后别见我的妻子 你能做到吗
I can do that.
我能
Wow。That's great.
哇 太棒了
Thank you.
谢谢你
I gotta go to Vegas tonight.
要知道我今晚得去拉斯维加斯
Some business meeting tomorrow.
明天还有会要开
I really don't want to be worrying about…
我真的不想心里还惦记着…
- you know。- Yeah.
- 你懂的 - 嗯
Thank you.
谢谢你
I really appreciate it.
我很感激
「Need to see you。Urgent。Bagels.」
快来见我 急事 带点甜甜圈
（丽诺尔：拜托了）
Four bagels and some cream cheese，please.
来四个甜甜圈 再来点奶油干酪
Okay.
没问题
- Be careful。They're really hot。- Thanks.
- 小心烫手 - 谢谢
Hello？
有人吗
（甜甜圈）
Lennie？
莉妮
Lennie.
Jesus，God.
我的天
Lennie？Wake up！
莉妮 快醒醒
Come on，come on！
快醒醒 快醒醒
- Lennie！- Freeze！Don't move！
- 莉妮 - 住手 不许动
Step away from the knife.
离那把刀远一点
- Get your hands up！- Sir，back away，now.
- 把手举起来 - 先生 马上退后
I didn't do this.
这不是我干的
Get your hands up，now！
立刻把手举起来
Slowly.
慢点
Get your hands up.
手举起来
- You gotta listen to me。- On the floor，now！
- 你们得听我说 - 快跪下
Listen to me.
听我说
- Down on the floor！- Listen to me.
- 快跪下 - 听我说
- Step away from the knife！- On your knees。Now！
- 从那把刀旁边挪开 - 立刻跪下
Down！
跪下
Get your hands up！
把手举起来
Hands up！
手举起来
Hands up！Higher！
举起来 举高点
I didn't do this.
我是无辜的
Shit！Moving in！
该死 到那边去
He's there！
他在那
Hey！Hey！
嘿 嘿
Drop your weapon！
别动
Oh，he's heading west！
快点 他在往西面逃
He's heading north。22nd street。Back alley.
他正往树林跑 速度很快 请支援
Stop！
停下
Suspect in sight.
看到疑犯了
Go inside。I'm heading back.
进去 我马上就回来
Hey！
嘿
Hey！Police！
嘿 警察
Door's sealed！
不许动
- Door is sealed。Shit！- I just saw him inside.
- 门被封住了 靠 - 我刚刚看见他在里面
Clear！Moving in！
安全 我进去了
You see him anywhere？
你看见他了吗
He disappeared.
他不见了
God damn it。He's gone.
该死 他逃掉了
This is 103。Suspect is gone.
这里是103 嫌疑人逃跑了
∮ The sun is old on water ∮
∮ 夕阳落水 ∮
∮ Yearling flakes keep whirling by ∮
∮ 波澜四起 ∮
∮ Carry me，me awry ∮
∮ 载我远行 恍恍荡荡 ∮
∮ Collapsing breaths discover ∮
∮ 惊涛骇浪 不绝于耳 ∮
∮ Turning hope，new-boarded highs ∮
∮ 重拾希冀 翻阅新篇 ∮
∮ Receding howls dew the skies ∮
∮ 潮起潮落 响彻天际 ∮
Yeah.
喂
Kim，it's Dad.
金姆 是爸爸
Where are you？
你在哪里
I'm at Mom's.
我在妈妈这儿
Looking for my yellow sweater.
在找我的黄色毛衣
Are you alone？
你一个人吗
Stuart is in Vegas。Why？
斯图尔特在拉斯维加斯 怎么了
I have something to tell you.
我有事要告诉你
Dad？
爸
Dad，what's wrong？
爸 出什么事了
Something terrible has happened.
有可怕的事情发生了
And I want you to hear it from me first.
我想先亲口告诉你
Your mom…
你妈妈…
She's dead.
她去世了
Someone murdered her…
有人谋杀了她
in my apartment.
在我的公寓里
It looks like I did it.
看起来像是我杀的
I don't know why。I don't know who.
我不知道为什么也不知道是谁干的
But I'm going to find out.
但是我会找到真相的
Listen carefully，Kim.
听清楚了 金姆
No matter what anyone says，don't trust them.
不管别人说什么 不要相信他们
- No。- You hear？
- 别 - 明白了吗
- I'll find a way to contact you。- But Dad…
- 我会想办法联系你的 - 爸
Try to be strong.
坚强一点
- Dad？- I love you.
- 爸 - 我爱你
Wait.
等等
You know，you need to check this out，alright？
你得检查一下这个 好吗
Sergeant Dotzler，suspect's name is Bryan Mills.
多兹勒警长 嫌疑人名叫布莱恩·米尔斯
- His？- His.
- 他的吗 - 对
Not his.
不是他的
（加州驾照）
The officers arrived on the scene because…
你的警官为什么能碰巧看见他
Anonymous call came in，
我们接到了电话
reported a woman screaming…
声称听到一个女人尖叫
「He's killing me。He's killing me.」
「他要杀我 他要杀我」
Her name is Lenore St。John.
她名叫丽诺尔·圣约翰
We sent a car to her address。It was listed on her license.
我们根据她证件上的地址派了一辆警车
Her daughter was there，but her husband was in Las Vegas on business.
她的女儿在那里 但是她的丈夫在拉斯维加斯出差
He's… taking the first flight home.
他会 呃 乘最早的一班航班回家
- Any witnesses？- We're canvassing now.
- 有证人吗 - 摄像头什么都没有拍到
Call came from an unlisted number.
电话来自于未登记的号码
We're checking out the cells as well.
我们也会查一下他们的手机
Download both of the phones，correlate the data.
把这两台手机的信息都下载下来 整理数据
I want to know when these two people…
我想知道这两人什么时候…
spoke，texted，emailed.
聊天 发短信 发邮件
Every form of communication.
任何形式的联系都要
Dates，times…
时间 次数
duration of calls.
通话时长
Let's bag this.
把这些打包带走
Detective，bag that.
警探 把它打包
（甜甜圈）
What's wrong？
有什么不对劲的吗
Good.
味道不错
Right now，this is still a very active crime scene.
我现在正在一起刚刚发生的犯罪现场
Investigators have been here on the scene
调查员们在现场待了一整个上午
all morning，but so far…
但是到目前为止
police have not told us what happened inside the apartment…
警方还没有告诉我们该公寓里到底发生了什么
where earlier this morning… a woman's body was discovered.
今晨这里发现了一具女性尸体
Bryan Mills is the owner of the apartment…
布莱恩·米尔斯是这家公寓的户主
and the ex-husband of the deceased.
同时也是受害者的前夫
- Who's this？- It's me.
- 谁啊 - 是我
You're on the news.
你上新闻了
I didn't do it，Sam.
不是我干的 萨姆
Obviously，you didn't do it。Are you all right？
显然不是你啊 你还好吗
I'm going down the rabbit hole。The code still the same？
我要去次秘密基地 密码没变吧
Yeah。It's still the same.
是啊 是啊 丝毫未变
- I'll be in touch。- Be careful.
- 我会保持联系的 - 小心点
So，this is the area we lost him，sir.
这里就是我们跟丢他的地方 长官
The guy vanished.
他就这么消失不见了
That's the gun that he took… off one of our officers，sir.
这把就是他从我们一位警官那儿抢来的枪 长官
He had a gun，and he didn't fire at you？
他有枪 他还没有朝你开枪
No，sir.
没有 长官
And the helicopters…
那直升机呢
saw nothing？
什么都没看到
Choppers didn't see anything，sir。No.
直升机什么都没有发现 警长
I know he's good…
我知道他很厉害
but…
但是
vanishing into thin air？
怎么可能凭空消失
Let's move the truck.
来 把卡车移开
Do you know why your wife went to visit Mr。Mills？
你知道为什么你的妻子会去见米尔斯先生吗
No，I don't know.
不 我… 我不知道
Their relationship was mostly centered around their daughter.
你知道他们之间的关系主要是围绕他们的女儿吧
But I think…
但我觉得…
he wanted more than friendship.
他想要的不止是朋友关系
I asked her to speak to him…
我叫她去和他谈谈…
and tell him that he should stop bothering her about it.
让他别再来为此打扰她的生活了
So you think that's what she was doing over there？
所以你认为这就是为什么她会过去
I don't know.
我不知道
What are you doing？
你们在干什么
Stuart，why are they going through all of Mom's stuff？
斯图尔特 为什么他们在翻妈妈的东西
Hey，Kim.
嘿 金姆
Miss St。John，Frank Dotzler.
圣约翰女士 在下是弗兰克·多兹勒
Mills。My name is Mills.
米尔斯 我姓米尔斯
Sorry for all the chaos.
抱歉打扰了
We're just looking around to see if we can find something to help us.
我们只是想看看有没有能帮助查案的线索
I know what you're looking for.
我知道你们在找什么
I would just really like
我希望他们
them out of her bedroom for a few minutes.
能离开我妈妈的卧室几分钟
Garcia，let's vacate the bedroom.
加西亚 撤出卧室里的人
Everybody out of the bedroom.
大家都从卧室里出来
Thank you.
谢谢
If I could just have a few minutes of your time。Ask you a few questions.
你能挤出点时间和我聊聊吗 我想问你一些问题
Why aren't you out there trying to find out who did this…
你为什么不在外面寻找凶手
instead of just standing around，going through our home？
而不是在我们家乱晃
We have people out there looking.
我们派了人在外寻找
But in order for me to get a full picture…
但是为了让我能把握全局
I have to ask questions of him。I have to ask questions of you.
我得问他还有你一些问题
My mom went to see my dad。I don't know why.
我妈妈去见我爸爸了 我不知道为什么
Probably to talk about me.
可能是为了聊我的事吧
Look，there's just…
听着 只是…
He didn't do it.
不是他干的
He just didn't。He didn't do it.
不是他 不是我爸
There's no way on earth he would lay a hand on her。Just，don't.
我爸绝对不可能…
He loved her.
他爱她
That's all I know.
我只知道这些
Please.
别碰
That's mine。That's not even hers.
是我的 不是我妈的
Excuse me.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不好意思
Oh，God.
天啊
Come on，let's get you home.
来吧 我们把你送回家
If something comes to mind，anything at all…
如果你想到什么 请联系我们
It might not be anything.
你知道这可能不算什么
You know what happened in Paris
在巴黎和伊斯坦布尔发生了什么吗
and Istanbul a couple years ago where Bryan saved his family.
几年前 布莱恩救了他的家人
Sure。You think that's connected to this？
当然 你觉得和这事有联系吗
I never really wanted to know all the details…
要知道我从来不想了解那些细节…
but a lot of people ended up dead and now this.
但是很多人为此失去了性命 现在又发生了这件事
So what you're telling me is…
所以你想说的是…
I'm dealing with a very dangerous man.
我面对的是一个十分危险的人
No.
不
No。Bryan's not dangerous.
布莱恩并不危险
The world he lives in is.
但他所生活的世界却很危险
He loves his family…
他爱他的家庭
but he has a lot of enemies.
但他树敌不少
I see.
我明白了
Bring him into Room Three.
把他带到3号房间
Garcia will… get you back home.
加西亚会把你送回家
Thank you.
谢谢
（丽诺尔·圣约翰）
This guy's a ghost.
这家伙像幽灵一样
At 21，he's in the army.
他21岁时 入伍
At 23，he joins Special Forces.
23岁时 加入了特种部队
Then he's gone.
然后就消失了
No service record.
没有服役记录
No discharge.
没有退役记录
Nothing。Nothing.
什么都没有 全是空白
Sounds like spy shit to me.
听起来像是个间谍
Until we have another suspect，he's our man.
而且直到我们找到其他的嫌疑人 他就是头号嫌犯
So here's our best way of finding him。His daughter with the deceased.
这是我们能找到他的最好方法 他和被害人的女儿
Her husband says that he's really close to her.
被害人丈夫说他和他的女儿关系十分亲密
Devoted to her.
全身心地爱她
So let's keep a close watch on her.
所以我们密切监视她
Where she goes，who she calls，who she talks to.
她去哪里 打给谁电话 和谁交流
Let's not screw this up，okay？
别把这事搞砸了 明白了吗
So，this is gonna be our best shot at finding him.
因为这就是我们找到他的最好机会了
Do we have the deceased's car？
被害人的车呢
Yeah，that just came in。They have his，too.
刚送来 布莱恩的也有
All right。Garcia，Smith.
好的 加西亚 史密斯
Let's do a full sweep of the car.
仔细搜查那辆车
GPS downloaded，see where he went and when.
下载GPS记录 找到它何时在何处
See if they correlate.
看看是否有关联
See if we can find out what's going on.
看看我们能否发现到底发生了什么事
Just came in，his and hers.
他们俩的车刚刚送到
Let's go，then.
那我们去看看
Follow me.
跟着我
So，what's this about？
所以到底发生什么事了
Some guy offed his ex.
有人杀掉了他的前妻
Allegedly.
据说是这样
Right。Allegedly.
没错 据说是这样
（GPS记录 下载中）
- He didn't do her in the car，did he？- No，in his house.
- 不是在车里杀的吧 - 不是 在他家里
Good。I hate going in those after.
太好了 我讨厌事后处理那种东西了
Blood。Pieces of flesh and shit。It's disgusting.
血迹 恶心死人的尸体啊什么的
（GPS记录 下载完成）
Which GPS you want done first？
你们想先弄哪部车的GPS
His，then hers.
他的 再弄她的
Right over here.
就在这儿
（丽诺尔·圣约翰 GPS记录）
（晚上10点04分 兰乔）
（兰乔加油站）
What the hell were you doing all the way out there，Lenore？
丽诺尔 你到底去那里干什么
（兰乔加油站）
Excuse me.
不好意思
Inspector Mallory，LAPD.
我是洛杉矶警局的的马丽警官
We're following up on a missing persons investigation.
我们在调查一个失踪的人
I was wondering if you'd seen this woman.
想知道你是否见过这个女人
She was here about 10 p.m。last night.
昨晚约十点的时候她到过这儿
I was here then.
我昨晚上班的
I didn't see her。I didn't see hardly nobody.
但没看见她 几乎没有看见任何人
Not exactly a bustling destination，if you know what I mean.
这里不是个买东西的好地方 你懂的
Hey，Sally.
嘿 萨拉
Excuse me.
不好意思
Duty calls.
有活了
Amanda？
阿曼达
Excuse me.
抱歉
Inspector Mallory，LAPD.
我是洛杉矶警局的的马丽警官
Are these security cameras operative or are they just there for show？
这些监控摄像头在运行还是只是装装样子
Yeah，they work.
没错 它们在运行
Follow me.
跟我来
You have the tape from yesterday？
你有昨天的监控录像带吗
No，I wasn't here。The other guy was.
不 昨天不是我上班 是另一个人
But if someone was here，it will be on there.
但只要有人 就肯定留了录像
Just push that button for the playback.
按那个按钮回放即可
I'm just gonna stay here while you look at that.
你看的时候我就待在这儿
（小老弟监视系统）
（3号摄影机画面）
You have problems with this system？
这个系统有问题吗
Breaks down sometimes.
有的时候会坏掉
They keep saying they're gonna replace it.
他们一直说要换掉它
Excuse me.
不好意思
Have you seen this woman？
你见过这个女人吗
You fellas should get more coordinated.
你们这群人得协调好啊
Coordinated？What do you mean？Like，color-coordinated？
协调 你什么意思 协调好衣服颜色
No，like，one of your guys was just in here asking the same thing.
不是 你们的人刚来这儿问我相同的问题
- One of our guys？- Yeah.
- 我们的人？- 没错
- Him？- Yeah。Him.
- 他 - 是啊 就是他
Took off to the gas station.
去了加油站
Freeze！
不许动
Mr。Mills？
米尔斯先生
Freeze！
不许动
- Step out，buddy。- Get out of the room.
- 出来 哥们 出来 - 快点出去
Freeze！
不许动
Stop what you're doing，Mr。Mills！
停下手里的动作 米尔斯先生
Step away from the desk！
离开那张桌子
Back away from the desk，sir.
离开那桌子
Step away from that desk，or I'll shoot you！
快点退后 我会开枪的
- I'll shoot。- Step away from the God damn desk，now！
- 我开枪了 - 马上给老子退后
Step away one step from the desk.
退后一步 离开那桌子
Just keep your hands where we can see them.
把手举起来 让我们看到你的手
Stay perfectly still.
站住别动
You know the drill.
你知道程序的
Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law.
你所说的一切都将成为呈堂证供
You have the right to an attorney…
你有权请律师
If you don't have one present during questioning…
如果你付不起律师费的话…
Brooks。All right.
我是布鲁克斯 好的
Garcia and Smith.
是加西亚和史密斯
They got him.
他们逮到他了
- Garcia。- Yeah，just picked him up.
- 逮到了 - 是的 刚刚逮捕的
Easy-peasy.
简单极了
If he's a pro like you said…
如果他真的跟你说的一样
he wasn't on his game today.
专业的也有失手的时候
- He's playing you！- What are you talking about？
- 他是在耍你 - 你说什么
Where is he？Where is he？
他现在在哪里 在哪里
He's back in Phillips' car。Why？
菲利普斯看着呢 怎么了
- Stop the cars！- What？
- 停车 - 什么
Stop the cars！
都停车
Now！
马上
Oh，come on！
拜托
- Phillips。- Yeah？
- 菲利普斯 - 怎么了
Our boss has got a hair up his ass about something.
头儿貌似有什么不好的预感
Just keep an eye on this guy，all right？
盯紧点那家伙 懂吗
Yeah，okay.
好的 没问题
- They think we're idiots。- It's unbelievable.
- 他们还以为我们是白痴 - 真不敢相信
He acts like I've never done this before.
他说的好像我从来没抓过人一样
He's just being Dotzler.
多兹勒就那样
You know what it is？He's a control freak.
才不是 知道为什么吗 他就是个控制狂
If he's not doing it himself，he's not happy.
如果不是他亲手抓的人 他就不开心
Keep driving！
继续开
Phillips！
菲利普斯
Come on.
快点
- Oh，my God！- You see that？What the hell is he doing！？
- 天啊 - 看见没 他到底想干嘛
Pull it over！
停车
Back it up！
倒车
Get out of the car！
下车
Drive！
开车
Stop the car.
停车
Come on，move.
快点 下车
Radio.
无线电
Cell phone.
手机
This is gonna end bad for you.
你这下子没好果子吃了
Don't be such a pessimist.
别这么悲观
Connecting to LAPD protected files.
接入加州警局警员档案
（已连接服务器 传输进度）
（数据传输中）
All units，code 10-29
呼叫所有警员追捕嫌犯
on a police car number 706.
他正驾驶尾号706的警车
Number 706.
尾号706
Suspect in sight.
发现嫌疑犯
Here，here！
在那 在那
Send some backup，now！
快点 就位 就位
（传输完成）
Dotzler.
我是多兹勒
By now，I'm sure you know who I am.
现在你知道我是谁
You know what I'm capable of.
有什么能耐了
I am beginning to.
我现在有点了解了
Let me ask you something，just so I'm clear.
我问你个问题 这样我就能明白了
CIA operative？Division 6？Division 7？What？
你66 67年是中情局特工 对吧
All you have to know is I'm innocent.
你只要知道我是无辜的就行
Give me two days，I can prove it.
给我两天时间 我证明给你看
I can find out who did it.
我会找出真凶的
You may very well be innocent，Mr。Mills.
你很有可能是无辜的 米尔斯先生
But that's the court's job to decide，it's not mine.
但这由法庭来决断 跟我无关
My job…
我要做的就是…
is to bring you in and let the law take its course，that's it.
把你送上法庭 让事实说话 仅此而已
Good luck.
那祝你好运了
I got a GPS on the phone。He's heading north.
我有那通电话的定位了 他朝南部走了
You want me to send units？
你要我派人过去吗
Don't bother。He's gone.
不用麻烦了 他已经消失了
- It's a dead end。- Wait，wait.
- 这线索断了 - 等等
Why does he want us to have this？
他为什么把这个留给我们
- He fucked up。- This guy doesn't fuck up.
- 他失手了 - 这家伙可不会失手
He wants us to watch it.
他想要我们看录像
Why？
为什么
I don't know yet.
我暂时不知道
Who is she waiting for？
她在等谁
Who are these guys？
这些人是谁
- Holy shit！- Who are these guys？
- 天啊 - 这些人是谁
Give me our tech guy。I need some magic done on a security tape。Now。Right now.
我有监控录像要处理 立刻马上派个技术人员过来
Hey，let me guess.
嘿 我猜猜
Pileup on the 710 North.
710北线严重堵车
Massive clusterfuck of police vehicles 15 miles headed south.
被大量警车向南追捕15英里
Sounds about right.
大概就是这样
Hey，thanks，Sam.
嘿 谢谢 萨姆
You want to tell me what's going on？
你打算告诉我怎么回事吗
Lenore sent me a text.
丽诺尔发了短信给我
Asked to come over to my place for bagels.
想来我家吃甜甜圈
I got the bagels.
我出门买了
When I came back，I found her car out front.
等回来的时候 我看到她的车停在门前
And，She was in my bed with her throat slashed.
然后 她被人割了喉咙 死在我的床上
Oh，Jesus.
天啊
What else？
还有什么
I found a location on her car's GPS
我从她车里的GPS
from the night before.
发现了昨晚她去的地方
She was out at this gas station in the middle of nowhere.
她到了一个荒无人烟的加油站
I saw it on a security camera.
我看了那边的监控录像
She was snatched.
她是被绑架走的
What do you want us to do？
你需要我们做什么
I downloaded all her phone records from the police files。And mine.
我从警局档案里下载了她所有的电话记录 目前还在查
Maybe there's something there.
也许里面会有什么信息
I need analysis of this.
我之前还没注意
Her hair。Might turn up something，might turn up nothing.
她的头发 也许有用 也许没用
Anything else？
还有什么其他的吗
I want to go to the funeral.
我想去参加她的葬礼
The Bible constantly tells us…
圣经一直告诉我们
that there will be difficult times in life…
生命中总是充满了艰辛
when we feel like we are walking…
当我们走在黑暗无光
through a dark，dangerous valley.
危机四伏的小道时
- Valley of the shadow of death。- Are you OK？
- 一条死气沉沉的小道时 - 你还好吧
But what the word of God does make very clear…
但是全能的上帝却说得很清楚
is that，as we move through such times…
当我们经历这种情形的时候
「the Lord is my shepherd.
上帝会指引我们
「He maketh me to lie down in green pastures.
直到安全的彼岸
「He leadeth me beside still waters.」
他会引领我们走过困境
In the name of the Father…
以圣父
and of the Son…
圣子
and of the Holy Spirit.
圣灵之名
Are you holding up？
你知道了吧
Right there.
那边
Get me sound on that。Right there.
把音频调出来 就那个人的
Kim，I'm so sorry.
金姆 对不起
If there's anything we can do…
如果我们能帮什么忙的话…
Hey.
嘿
We're there for you.
我们都在
You know that，right？
你知道的 对吧
- Hey，baby。- Hey.
- 嘿 宝贝 - 嘿
I just want to go home.
我就想回家而已
You hear that？
你听到了吗
You hear that click？
听到杂音了吗
Yeah。We're getting some interference somewhere.
听到了 我这边接收到一些电子干扰
There it goes again.
他去跟金姆说话了
- Hey。- Hi.
- 嘿 - 嗨
Oh，sweetie.
宝贝
They're jamming our signal.
他们在干扰我们的信号
I know。I know.
我知道 我知道
I'm so，so sorry.
我真的觉得很难过
Listen.
听着
He'll be in touch.
他会联络你
Just stick to your schedule.
和以前日常作息一样就行
Your very predictable schedule.
按你最循规蹈矩的作息就行
（无讯号）
You want me to put a tail on them？
你想要我跟踪他吗
No，it's a waste of time。It'd be a waste of our money.
不用了 浪费时间而已 他们总有办法的
These guys could lose a tail
就算你派警犬去
if it was attached to a dog.
他们还是能甩掉
We're done.
我们完事了
Cut the feed.
切了吧
Stuart，why are there still…
斯图尔特 为什么还是有…
Why are there still cops camped outside？
为什么家外面还是有警察
I think it's standard operating procedure.
我估计是他们的标准流程吧
They think my dad's going to show up here？Are they stupid or something？
你觉得我爸会来这里吗 他们是傻还是什么
I don't know what they think.
我也不知道他们想怎么样
Inspector Dotzler asked if we minded and I said no.
多兹勒警长问我介不介意 我说不介意
You should have asked me。I mind.
那你也应该问问我 我介意
I'm sorry.
对不起
And who's he？
他是谁
Well，we um… We need protection.
我们… 我们需要保护
Kim，honey，
金姆 宝贝
I know it's hard on you，but it's hard on me，too.
我知道你心里肯定很难过 其实我也是
I'm sorry。I didn't realize it was a competition.
不好意思 我都不知道 原来是在比谁更可怜
It's not a competition.
这不是比可怜
Please，don't hate me.
求你了 别记恨我
I'm not responsible for what happened.
发生这一切也不能怪我啊
I don't hate you，Stuart.
我不恨你 多兹勒
But for the last two years…
但近两年来
every time I looked into my mom's eyes…
我每次看到妈妈
the only thing I saw was hurt and sadness.
她都是那副受伤可怜的眼神
And for that…
就凭这点
I do hold you responsible.
你绝对要负责
- Where are you going？- School.
- 你这是要去哪里 - 去学校
If I'm allowed.
如果还允许我去的话
I got you，baby。I got you.
我跟着你呢 宝贝 我跟得上
- Why are you following me？- It's for your own protection，miss.
- 你为什么要跟着我 - 是为了你自己的安全 小姐
Protection？From who？My father？
安全？谁会威胁我？我爸？
You really think my father would hurt me？
你们真的觉得我爸会伤害我吗
Your mother probably didn't think so either.
你妈妈之前估计也没想到吧
Asshole.
贱人
- Hey。- Hey.
- 嗨 - 嘿
（喝掉我）
Anything？
有什么情况吗
She's on campus。You want me to follow？
她在学校了 你要我跟着吗
- Is the bug active？- Yes.
- 监听器还在吗 - 在的
and listen。If he shows up，we'll hear it.
听清楚了 如果他露面 我们马上赶到
- What else？- She went into this convenience store，
- 还有什么情况 - 她去了家便利店
chugged down a drink of some kind right from the fridge.
喝了一瓶饮料一样的东西
All right.
明白
Keep me informed.
随时报告情况
As you might remember，last week we discussed disassociations…
大家也许还记得 上周我们讨论了…
and interactions between dorsal and ventral streams… in object recognition.
视皮层背侧和腹侧 在感知物体认知时的区别和联系…
Now，a Dominant Hypothesis…
多普勒假说是指…
is that the dorsal stream is supporting motor interactions with objects.
视皮层背侧通路是用来感知物体运动的联系
While ventral stream structures extract visual information…
而腹侧通路则相对独立的构建
about the object that is independent.
关于物体的更多的视觉信息…
I'm feeling a little nauseous.
我有点想吐
Would you mind taking notes for me？
你能帮我记下笔记吗
- Yeah，sure。- Thanks.
- 没问题 - 谢谢
Now，in other words，object knowledge is represented in the ventral stream…
换言之 认知对象在腹侧通路中…
Excuse me。I wonder if you could… help me out with something？
不好意思 你能帮我个忙吗
- Sure。- There was a young woman in here…
- 没问题 - 这照片上的姑娘
- about an hour ago？- Oh，yeah。Poor kid.
- 一个小时前来过吗 - 来过啊 可怜的小家伙
- Does she come here often？- Every day.
- 她经常来吗 - 每天都来
- She bought what？- Same thing，a peach yogurt drink.
- 她买了什么 - 每天一瓶桃子酸奶
But today，she drank it all right there from the fridge.
但今天她在冰箱那边就喝完了
Must have been thirsty.
肯定是太渴了
You got anything？
什么情况
Yeah，she went to school。Got nauseous in class.
她去了学校 上课时觉得有点难受
Now she's on her way to the bathroom.
现在她去洗手间了
Call for back-up.
叫支援
I'm coming right now.
我马上过来
Here，Kim。Drink this.
金姆 把这个喝了
I put something in the yogurt to make you nauseous.
我在酸奶里放了让你难受的东西
This will take it away.
这能中和难受的感觉
Hi，baby.
嗨 宝贝
Hi.
嗨
Oh，Kim。Kim.
金姆
Oh，Kim.
Daddy。I don't know what to do.
爸 我不知道该怎么办
I'm pregnant.
我怀孕了
What？
什么
I'm pregnant.
我怀孕了
Dad？
爸
I'm okay.
我没事
I have low blood sugar.
我有低血糖
I haven't eaten since yesterday.
我从昨天开始就没吃过东西了
Eat this.
把这个吃了
Don't you worry.
别… 别担心
Let's get through this first and then…
我们先挺过眼下这关…
we'll figure out what's best for…
之后我们再从长计议
What you have to do is act natural.
金姆 你要做的就是自然点
This cop is really smart.
这些警察不蠢的
Anything out of the usual…
任何奇怪的举动
he'll become suspicious。Okay？
他们都会产生怀疑 懂了吗
I love you.
我爱你
I love you，too.
我也爱你
- Yes。- Where are you？
- 喂 - 你在哪里
I'm in the science building。East wing.
我在科学楼东翼
- She's in the bathroom。- Don't move。Wait for me.
- 她在厕所里 - 站着别动 等我
Where are you staying？
你现在住哪里
I'm still at Mom's.
我还在妈妈家里
I started packing her stuff.
我在整理她的遗物
It just… It doesn't feel real.
只是… 一切都太突然了
Oh，I know.
我懂的
I know.
我知道
Dad，there's…
爸 那是…
Stuart's been acting really weird.
斯图尔特最近真的很奇怪
He must be scared about something.
他一定是在害怕什么
He hired bodyguards.
他雇了保镖
Oh，my God.
天啊
It was so much fun。But you know what？
天啊 真有意思 但你知道吗
- He was such a jerk。- Really？
- 他就是这么个混蛋 - 真的？
He made me pay for my own drink at the bar.
在酒吧里 他让我付自己的酒钱
I did！I was wearing something more skimpy than this.
真的 我当时穿得比这还要暴露呢
- More skimpy than that？- I don't know what was happening.
- 比这还暴露吗 - 我都不清楚发生了什么
Maybe he's blind。I don't know.
也许他瞎了 我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道
- He is such a jerk。- I'm not gonna do it again，though.
- 他就是这么个混蛋 - 我不会再在那么做了
No，it's cool，I've seen him。I completely understand.
没关系 我看到他了 我完全理解
He's hot，right？
他很性感 对吧
- Go，go，go！- I'm going！
- 出去 出去 - 这就走
Go，go，go.
出去 出去 快出去
What the…
怎么
Excuse me？
干嘛
Perv！
色鬼
He just left.
他刚走
She's in the can.
她在厕所里
I can't let you leave.
我不能让你走
Seal all the areas.
封锁出口
Hey！
嘿
There he is.
他在那儿
Down the south corridor！
一定要拦住他
Freeze！
站住
Go，go，go！
快 快 快
Move！
出去
Just move！Come on！
快出去 快点
This way！Move，move！
这边 快跑 快跑
I know you think you're helping him…
我知道你认为自己在帮他
but you're not.
其实没有
You're not.
没有
Unless we get him to come in…
我们不建议你这么做
I can't start trying to make sense of what happened.
我没办法解释发生的事情
Someone killed my mom.
有人杀了我妈妈
That's what happened.
事情就是这样
It was not my father.
不是我爸爸干的
Without hearing his side of the story，they can't know that，can they？
我们还没听他的说辞 他们没办法了解 对吗
I do.
我知道
Is there anything else？
还有事吗
You know we can arrest you for obstructing an ongoing investigation？
我们能以你妨碍公务的名义逮捕你 你知道的吧
Arrest me.
逮捕我吧
Rather not.
我不想
Well，then，if you're not going to，
既然这样 如果你不逮捕我
can I go home？
那我能回家吗
Of course。Of course.
当然 当然
Thank you.
谢谢
Interesting family.
有趣的一家人
Don't worry，
别担心
we will take care of this。Do as we planned.
我们会搞定这事 按我们的计划去做
Call the car.
叫车
Where are we going，boss？
我们去哪儿 老大
The Malibu house.
马利布的房子
Okay，let's go get drunk.
好了 我们去喝酒吧
I'm not gonna hurt you.
我不会伤害你
I need a ride。Mind if I drive？
我需要搭车 我来开 好吗
Okay.
好
- What's your name？- Mike.
- 你叫什么名字 - 麦克
I'm Bryan。You have kids，Mike？
我叫布莱恩 你有孩子吗 麦克
Yeah，two.
有两个
- How old？- Owen is three，and Tori is seven.
- 几岁 - 欧文三岁 特里七岁
Great age.
这年纪不错
A piece of advice。Don't miss a day of it.
给你条建议 珍惜和他们相处的每一天
Before you know it，they'll be having kids of their own.
在你没反应过来之前 他们就会有自己的孩子了
Know what I mean？
明白我的意思吗
Thanks，Mike.
谢谢 麦克
You know，if you stand in a field with a book of matches…
当你带着一盒火柴 站在外面
you can have hundreds of rabbits in seconds like this.
你可以马上唤来成百上千只兔子
- You know how？- No.
- 知道怎么做到吗 - 不知道
Come in，all rabbits.
所有兔子 来报到
Come in，all rabbits。You like this？
所有兔子 来报到 就像这样
Who hired you？
谁雇的你
Who are you working for？
你在替谁做事
Your accent is shit！
你的口音真难听
Who are you working for？
你在替谁做事
I'd rather die than tell you.
我死也不告诉你
Scumbag！
蠢货
Boss？They're at the gate.
老大 他们在门口
Let them in.
让他们进来
Oh，and take a stroll.
哦 你出去会儿吧
I need a little privacy.
我要自己待会儿
Many？
曼尼
Oh！
哦
Bryan？
布莱恩
None of this is making sense to me，Stuart.
发生的这一切事 我看不明白 斯图尔特
I was hoping you could help me out.
我本来指望你能帮我
How did you…
你怎么…
Survive the crash？
没被撞死
The Russians who were following me when I was following you…
我在跟踪你的时候 那些俄国人在跟踪我
do they work for you，Stuart？
他们是你指使的吧 斯图尔特
No。I don't know what you're talking about.
不是 我不知道你在说什么
What do you know？
那你知道什么
The only thing I know is that you were fucking my wife.
我只知道你上了我老婆
And I know that she's dead！
我还知道她死了
No，no，no！
不 不 不要…
What do you know？
你知道什么
I don't know anything.
我什么都不知道
I swear。I don't know anything.
我发誓 我什么都不知道
- If I believed that，we wouldn't be here。- No！No！No！
- 我要是相信 我们就不会在这儿了 - 不 不 不
Malankov！
曼伦科夫
What？
什么
Malankov.
曼伦科夫
Oleg Malankov.
奥列格·曼伦科夫
Who is Oleg Malankov？
奥列格·曼伦科夫是谁
I owe him money.
我欠了他钱
You don't know him.
你不认识他
He'll never give up。It's only a game for him.
他绝不会放弃的 对他来说 只是游戏
I lost everything。He said he'd kill my family.
我输了一切 他说要杀了我的家人
Why didn't you tell this to the police？You let them think it was me.
你为什么不报警 你让他们以为人是我杀的
I was angry with you。God damn it，you promised！
我被你气疯了 你答应过
- You promised to stop seeing her！- So what do you think happened？
- 你答应不再见她的 - 你以为发生了什么
She came over to my place。This Malankov followed her there？
她到我那儿来 曼伦科夫跟她到了那儿
If you weren't seeing her behind my back…
要是你没有背着我见她
she wouldn't have been there in the first place，would she？
她根本就不会去你家 不是吗
They would have killed her someplace else.
他们会在别的地方杀她
So why are they coming after me？
那他们为什么要追杀我
Because I told them who you were.
因为我告诉了他们你以前的身份
That you would find them and kill them.
说你会找到并杀了他们
How convenient would that be for you？
这多便宜了你啊
I kill them，your debt is cancelled.
我杀他们 你的债就没了
I'm sorry，Bryan.
对不起 布莱恩
But I loved her。You gotta believe me.
但我爱她 你要相信我
I loved her！I loved her！
我爱她 我爱她
Here's what you're gonna do.
听着你要做什么
You're gonna go to the police and tell them everything.
你去找警察 告诉他们一切
I can't.
不能
I can't。He's crazy。You don't know him.
不能 他是个疯子 你不了解他
You can do whatever the hell you want。Either way…
你想做什么都可以 反正…
I'm a dead man.
我也是个死人了
I'm dead.
我死定了
They kill you，they don't get paid.
他们杀了你 就收不回债了
You're not the one they're gonna come after next.
你不是他们下一个要追杀的人
Kim.
金姆
Hey.
嘿
Can I get your keys，please？
能把你的钥匙拿出来吗
Do you know what you're getting yourself into，man？
你知道自己在做什么吗 哥们
Yeah。As a matter of fact，I do.
知道 事实上 我很清楚
Could I get your keys and your phone，please？
能拿着你的钥匙和手机吗
You mind putting your hands on the steering wheel？
你能把手放在方向盘上吗
Or what？What are you gonna do？Shoot me？
不然怎样 你要干嘛 开枪打我
Left or right？
左腿还是右腿
Go ahead，put the cuffs on.
继续 把手铐起来
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
Dad！
爸爸
Let's go，Kim.
我们走 金姆
What's going on？
怎么回事
We're keeping you safe.
我在保护你
Sam？
萨姆
Hey，Kim。We're gonna get in the truck.
嘿 金姆 我们上车去
Hi，Kim.
你好 金姆
Let's go.
我们走
Bernard Harris.
伯纳德·哈里斯
He's a trained sniper.
他是个职业狙击手
Left the army at 24.
24岁离开军队
Nothing，nothing after that.
之后毫无记录
Nothing until he registers as one of three founders
直到他和其他两个人一起成立了
of something called Private Securities International.
所谓的国际私人安保公司
The other two being，Casey Mark，
另外两个人 一个叫凯西·马克
Navy Seal，eight years' service.
在海军陆战队服役八年
「Explosives expert.」 It's right there.
爆破专家 写着呢
Next time we hear from him，he's 45
我们再次找到他踪迹的时候
and Senior Vice President
他45岁 已经成为
of Private Securities International.
国际私人安保公司的副总裁
Sam Grossman，communications expert，
萨姆·格罗斯曼 通讯专家
a wizard，
是个行家
and he's the COO of Private Securities International.
他是国际私人安保公司的首席运营官
Now，our primary person of interest…
接下来 我们的头号疑犯
Bryan Mills.
布莱恩·米尔斯
is listed as an 「employee」 of Private…
是国际私人安保公司的「雇员」
You get the picture.
你们明白了
These are very serious people.
这些人非常厉害
If you don't bring your A-game，
如果你们不全力以赴
they're gonna run around you，through you，under you.
他们就会把你们耍得团团转
I need it to stop right now.
我要你们立刻制止他们
There's one more thing。This.
还有一件事 看这个
The Russian，he killed himself.
这个俄国人 自杀了
Probably because he didn't wanna give up the information
也许是因为他不想把米尔斯想要的情报
that Mills was asking him for.
告诉他
Because obviously，he's not trying to kill you.
因为显然 他没想杀你
Obviously，he's not trying to kill anybody.
显然他没想杀任何人
He's only trying to get information.
他只是想收集情报
He's only trying to figure this out，just like we are.
他只是想弄清这件事 和我们一样
Except for the fact that he is a step ahead of us.
除了他领先了我们一步
I'd like to know the relationship between the Russians
我要弄清楚这些俄国人和他老婆的谋杀案
and the wife's murder.
之间的关系
One of these four people，they know something about it.
这四个人中 总有人知道些什么
They know the answer.
他们知道答案
I need you guys to find them.
我要你们找到他们
I need you to bring them in.
把他们带回来
（资料分析）
- Anything yet？- No.
- 找到线索了吗 - 没有
Nothing came up from the samples you gave me.
你给我的样本里什么也没有
But this is gonna take a while to sort through.
但是 梳理数据需要些时间
Bryan，there's a shitload of data here.
布莱恩 数据太多了
What is that？
那是什么
I downloaded the police computers.
我下载了警方电脑的信息
- For what？- The first thing they're gonna look at are the phone records to
- 做什么 - 他们首先会看通话记录
see if there are any clues.
寻找线索
Mine and Lenore's.
我和丽诺尔的
What's it gonna tell you，that you and Lenore spoke to each other？
那会说明什么 你和丽诺尔互相通话
You know what？Don't worry about it。We're almost done here anyway.
你知道吗 不要担心 我们就快结束了
So，what's the plan？
计划是什么
The plan is to make sure my daughter is safe.
计划是保证我女儿的安全
And the only way to do that，so it seems…
而唯一的办法 看来就是
is to eliminate the thing that will make her unsafe.
清除对她不利的东西
Malankov.
曼伦科夫
Good one，Stuart.
聪明 斯图尔特
I'd like to help.
我想帮忙
Oh，you're gonna help，all right。Like bait helps to catch a shark.
你会帮忙的 对吧 就像诱饵帮助捕鲨鱼
Excuse me？
什么
Start talking about Malankov.
先说说曼伦科夫
I want to know every detail.
我要知道每个细节
Who he is，what he does，where he lives…
他是谁 做什么 住哪儿
where he works.
工作地点
Oleg Malankov.
奥列格·曼伦科夫
He's as tough as they come.
他非常强悍
He served in the Russian Army
苏联侵略阿富汗时
when they invaded Afghanistan.
他在军队服役
He was Spetsnaz.
加入了斯佩茨纳兹（前苏联特种部队）
It's like our Navy SEALS.
就像我们的海豹突击队
After the collapse of the Soviet Union，
当时每个人都在抢夺他们能抢夺的东西
when everyone was grabbing what they could…
苏联解体后
there was a real demand for men with his kind of skills.
有他这样技术的人有大量的需求
He became one of the grabbers.
他成了掠夺者之一
I met him when I was doing a deal involving heavy machinery.
我在做重型机械生意时 遇见了他
Since then，we did business on a number of different occasions.
自那以后 我们在很多不同的场合做生意
Some deals worked out.
有些交易很成功
I don't have the money.
我没有钱
Last one didn't.
但最后一次失败了
What？
什么
My mom is dead because of one of your shitty business deals？
我妈妈是因为你一单失败的生意而死
No.
不
Kim，that's not what happened.
金姆 不是这样的
Fuck you！
你去死
We need him.
我们需要他
Call him.
给他打电话
Why？
为什么
Because you're gonna set him up for me.
因为你要约他 为我设个局
Make the call。Now.
打电话 马上
On speaker.
开扬声器
Pow.
砰
Stuart。I've missed you.
斯图尔特 我一直在想你
I have your money.
我筹足钱了
You have it？
有钱了
That was fast.
挺快的
How can I trust you？
我怎么相信你
You can trust me.
你可以相信我
Where do you want me to bring it？
你想我把钱带去那儿
Meet me at the building downtown.
在市中心的楼里见我
In one hour.
大约一小时后见
Sure，one hour.
好 一小时
Scumbag！
人渣
Tell me how his security works.
跟我说说安保情况
Malankov works out of his penthouse apartment.
曼伦科夫 他在他的顶层豪华公寓办公
He has a private elevator with two bodyguards.
他有一个私人电梯和两个保镖
Malankov is coming。Send the elevator.
曼伦科夫来了 让电梯下去
The elevator is controlled by security upstairs.
电梯是由楼上的安保控制的
Once they see who's inside the elevator and give the okay…
他们看见电梯里的人 并按下确认键
they will send the elevator up.
把电梯升上去
Outside the elevator，upstairs…
楼上的电梯外是安保室
is a security station and three more bodyguards.
还有另外三个保镖
Two sets of doors.
和两重门
Through the second set of doors is Malankov's private apartment.
穿过第二重门就是曼伦科夫的私人公寓
Can you help me out，here？I got an address but I don't have a name.
嘿 你能帮我个忙吗 这个单子只有地址 没有名字
- I got a back full of perishables。- Go to the first floor and ask for the desk.
- 车后面还有很多易腐食品 - 去一楼问前台 好吗
- First floor。Thank you so much。- You're welcome.
- 一楼 非常感谢 - 不客气
Hello，sir.
先生 你好
I'm here to see Oleg Malankov.
我来见奥列格·曼伦科夫
Okay，sir，have a good day.
好的 先生 祝您愉快
Thanks.
谢谢
Get out.
出去
It's Dotzler.
是多兹勒
Answer it。Act normal.
接电话 表现得正常点
Don't try anything smart.
别耍小聪明
- Hello？- Mr。St。John？
- 你好 - 圣约翰先生
Frank Dotzler.
我是弗兰克·多兹勒
Where are you？
你在哪里
I'm in a business meeting。Is there anything wrong？
我在开会呢 有什么事吗
Bryan Mills removed your stepdaughter from your home.
布莱恩·米尔斯 把你的继女从家里带走了
I'm there right now.
我现在就在你家这里
Oh，my God。That's…
哦 天啊 那…
- When are you coming home？- I'm leaving immediately.
- 你什么时候回家 - 我现在就出发
It should take me about an hour to get there from where I am.
从我这里过去 大概需要一个小时的时间
- Where exactly is that？- Malibu.
- 你现在在哪 - 我在马利布
Listen，Inspector，I don't think he means her any harm.
听我说 我觉得他对她没有恶意 他…
Mr。St。John，this man is the prime suspect in the murder of your wife.
圣约翰先生 这个人是谋杀你妻子的主要嫌疑人
His associates held guns on my men
他的同伙在你家门口
in the front of your home.
拿着枪指着我的人
As far as I'm concerned，he is dangerous and has to be taken into custody.
在我看来 他很危险 而且必须抓住他
So，if you'd like，I can send a car for you，
所以如果你需要 我可以派车去接你
but I need you somewhere safe.
但是你得呆在一个安全的地方
No，no，no。It's fine.
不 不 不 没事的
I'm leaving right now.
我现在就出发
I'll be waiting for you.
我会等着你的
Get me a location on St。John's phone.
给我定位一下圣约翰的手机
As soon as he finds out you're not in Malibu，
一旦他发现你不在马利布
he'll be headed right here.
他就会马上跑到这里来
I'd say we have
照我说
less than 30 minutes to do this before he shows up.
在他出现之前 我们只有不到30分钟的时间行动
It's enough time for me.
这点时间对我来说够了
Can you handle this，Kim？
金姆 你能操作这个吗
What do I have to do？
你要我做什么
Just keep me up to date on what comes up.
不管有什么事 随时向我报告就可以了
Thanks，Sam.
谢谢 萨姆
Inspector，the tape you gave us from that gas station…
督察 这是你给我们的加油站的监控录像
here are the stills，frame by frame.
这些是截图 一帧一帧的
Hey.
嘿
He lied to you about where he was.
关于他在哪里 他向你撒谎了
- What a surprise。- He's downtown.
- 真意外 - 他在市区
Let's call out the cavalry.
我们去抓那家伙
All right.
好的
We're out of this location！We're on the move！Let's go！
找到他的位置了 我们走 我们走
They're gone.
他们走了
Okay。Cops on the move.
好的 条子们出发了
Okay。Let's go.
好的 我们走
You do exactly as you were told.
一切按计划行事
Don't improvise.
不要临场发挥
Try anything funny，and they'll kill you.
你要是耍花招 他们会杀了你的
And if they don't，I will.
而且就算他们不杀 我也会杀了你
I don't know how many times I can say sorry.
我不知道我能说多少次对不起
Come here，Kim.
过来 金姆
There.
看这里
（布莱恩·米尔斯短信下载）
Dotzler.
我是多兹勒
I found out something you might wanna know.
我发现了一些你可能感兴趣的东西
Matching insurance policies on St。John and his wife.
我们对比了圣约翰和他妻子的保险
$12 million。Each.
两个人各投了1200万
How about that？
怎么样
Stuart St。John。Mr。Malankov's expecting me.
我是斯图尔特·圣约翰 曼伦科夫先生在等我
What's in the bag？
那个包里有什么
We're in.
我们黑进去了
Okay.
好的
Stuart St。John is clear。Unlock the elevator.
斯图尔特·圣约翰没问题 把电梯解锁
Okay.
好的
Got him.
搞定
Go！All right.
走 好的
What's going on？
怎么了
Everything okay？
一切正常吗
Call the elevator.
给控制电梯的打电话
Get back to the truck.
回到货车上
Bingo.
好了
Right on.
搞定了
He's coming up.
他上来了
Go，go，go.
走 走 走
Showtime。Bingo.
好戏上演了
What the hell's going on？
他妈的发生什么了
Guys？
各位
Go check it out.
去看看
Get up.
起来
Get up！
Who are you，old man？
你这老头子是谁
You killed my ex-wife.
你杀了我的前妻
But you're not gonna kill my daughter.
但是我不会让你杀了我的女儿的
Your daughter？
你的女儿
Shit！
卧槽
We are fucked by the same man.
我们被同一个人耍了
What are you talking about？
你在说什么
Stuart St。John.
斯图尔特·圣约翰
First，he gets me to kill your wife…
他先让我去杀了你的妻子
then you.
然后再来杀你
And when that doesn't work…
如果不成功
he pushes you to kill me，no？
他就让你来杀我
Either way，he wins.
不管怎样他都赢了
Your wife was just part of a business deal like many before her.
你的妻子只是一场交易的一部分 就像很多在我之前的人一样
It is my turn to lose the game.
现在轮到我输了
Finish me！
杀了我吧
Finish me.
I deserve it.
我活该
Yes.
是的
You do.
你是活该
（我需要和你见面 晚上10点 在兰乔加油站见 我是布莱恩）
（妈妈被杀那晚 你手机给她发短信 约她在兰乔加油站见面 有人用了你手机）
Dad？
爸爸
Listen.
听我说
- Dad？- What is it，Kim？
- 爸爸 - 怎么了
No！
不
Sam！Sam！
萨姆 萨姆
Kim.
金姆
Come on。Let's go.
快点 我们走 我们走
- Come on。Move。- Kim！
- 快走 - 金姆
Get in the car！
进车子
Let's go，come on！
我们走 快点
Where are we going？
我们要去哪
Get in the car.
进车子
He's still alive。Let's get a medic in here… ASAP！Medic！
他还活着 叫个医务人员过来 让他马上就来
Inspector！
督察
The elevator！
看电梯
Dotzler，it's Smith。We're in Malankov's building.
多兹勒 我是史密斯 我们在曼伦科夫的地方
- I think… Mills is here。- Really？
- 我觉得米尔斯就在这里 - 真的吗
Yeah。We're gonna check the apartment now.
是的 我现在就去查一下这幢公寓
Shit！
该死
Hey！Can you move？
嘿 你还能动吗
Back it up。Back it up.
退几步 退几步
All right，let's go。Everybody in.
好吧 我们走 所有人都进来
Come on！Let's go！
来吧 我们走
This guy's still warm。We got a good chance he's still in the building.
他很有可能还在这幢楼里
Call downstairs，lock it up。Nobody in，nobody out.
呼叫楼下的人 封锁大楼 谁都不允许进出
Lock it up。Nobody in，nobody out.
封锁大楼 谁都不允许进出
「Text from your phone asking Mom to meet you…
在妈妈被杀那晚 你的手机给她发短信
「at the Rancho Berrego the night she died.
约她在兰乔加油站见面
「Someone used your phone？」
有人用了你的手机
（追踪金姆的手机中）
- Santa Monica Aviation。- This is Mr。St。John.
- 这里是圣塔莫妮卡航空 - 我是圣约翰
I'll be there in 15 minutes。Get the plane ready.
我15分钟之内到 把飞机准备好
It'll be ready.
好的
Why are you doing this？
你为什么要这么做
Because your father and his friends are homicidal maniacs.
因为你爸爸和他的朋友都是一群杀人狂
- You're a lying piece of shit。- Shut up.
- 你这坨满嘴胡话的屎 - 闭嘴
You killed her！I know…
我知道你杀了她
You shut up！
你他妈给我闭嘴
Shut up！
闭嘴
Brooks.
我是布鲁克斯
I want the full work-up on a black Porsche，license plate number 6-8-9-M-J-C-6.
我要你定位一辆黑色的保时捷 车牌号码689MJC6
Okay.
好的
Connect me to the Porsche phone and trace it.
帮我连上保时捷的车载电话并且定位
All right.
好的
I need a run on a California plate
我要搜寻一辆车 加州牌照
6-8-9-Mary-Jane-Charlie-6.
号码689MJC6
I need a phone，too.
还要他的电话号码
（陌生号码来电）
Pick up the phone.
接电话
Black Porsche's phone position received.
黑色保时捷车载电话已定位
Heading west.
正向西驶
Yes？
喂
Listen，Mr。Mills.
听我说 米尔斯先生
It's Dotzler.
我是多兹勒
I've started to piece this thing together.
我现在有点头绪了
There's two life insurance policies.
有两份人身安全保险
One for St。John，one for your ex-wife.
一份是圣约翰的 一份是你前妻的
You understand？
你听懂了吗
Stuart owed money to these Russians.
斯图尔特欠这些俄国人钱
A lot of it.
欠了很多
The ones who abducted her.
就是绑架她的那些人
Then they took her to my place
然后他们就把她带到我的家里杀掉
and killed her to keep me out of the way.
这样好让我没法妨碍他们
I need you to step back…
我要你放手
and allow me to handle this.
让我来处理这件事
I got it.
我能处理
What's your first priority here，Inspector？
对你来说哪件事最重要 督察
To arrest St。John
逮捕圣约翰
and charge him with your ex-wife's murder.
并以谋杀你前妻的罪名起诉他
My first priority is my daughter.
对我来说 最重要的是我的女儿
Get out of the car.
下车
Come on，let's go.
快点 我们走
Go！
走啊
（金姆手机位置 圣塔莫妮卡机场）
Okay，we're leaving now。Come on，let's go.
好了 我们现在就走 快 我们走
Yes，sir！
是 先生
（圣塔莫尼卡公路）
Approaching Runway Two.
跑道安全
Ready for takeoff.
可以起飞
Come on，guys。Let's go.
快点啊 快点 我们走
Requesting permission for takeoff.
请求允许起飞
We got a visual on the Porsche.
我们看到那辆保时捷了
He's heading to Santa Monica airport.
他正在前往圣塔莫妮卡机场
I want all units in the area of the Santa Monica airport…
所有小队到圣塔莫妮卡机场
to be on the lookout for a black Porsche.
监视一辆黑色的保时捷
49-90.
4990航班
Taxiways are closed.
滑行道已关闭
No.
不会吧
Let's go！
快 快
- Come on！- We don't have enough speed！
- 快点 - 起飞速度不够
Let's go！
快啊
Give me the goddamn gun！
他妈的把枪给我
I'll shoot you in the head！
我要打爆你的脑袋
Shut up！
闭嘴
Very smart…
真聪明
playing me off against the Russian.
骗我去干掉那群俄罗斯人
Coming over for coffee.
过来喝咖啡
Taking my phone，sending texts and then erasing them.
拿我的手机 发短信 然后把它们删除
（我需要和你见面 晚上10点 在兰乔加油站见 我是布莱恩）
So that your pals could plant Lenore's body…
这样你的同伙就可以把丽诺尔的尸体放我家
and make it look as if I killed her.
嫁祸我
（快来见我 急事 带点甜甜圈）
All your problems solved.
然后你的问题就解决了
All your worries over.
你什么都不用担心了
But it didn't quite work out that way.
但是事情不是这么来的
Oh，listen，Bryan.
听好了 布莱恩
They're coming.
他们要来了
You can't kill me now.
你现在可杀不了我了
Oh，yeah？
是吗
Dad…
爸爸
I know you know a lot of people…
我知道你认识很多人
and with a good lawyer，you'll get out of jail in a few years.
再找一个好一点的律师 你几年之内就可以出狱了
And then I'll come for you.
到那时我会来找你
I'll find you.
我会找到你
And we both know what's gonna happen.
我们都知道会发生什么事
I knew from the beginning.
我从一开始就知道
It was the bagels.
因为那些甜甜圈
They were warm.
它们是热的
I had to ask myself…
我不得不问自己…
what kind of guy goes out for warm bagels…
什么人会出去买几个热乎乎的甜甜圈…
and comes back and commits murder？
再回来杀人
So，I compared the timestamps to the deleted texts…
所以 我比较了那些你从我们电脑上下载的
that you downloaded from our computers.
被删除的短信的时间标签
Which，by the way，is illegal，and I could arrest you for it.
当然这是犯法的 我们可以为了这个逮捕你
I could。But it's got me.
我可以的 但这让我吃了一惊
And I was able to figure it out.
我能把这件事想通了
She was leaving him.
她要离开他了
He needed the insurance money to pay Malankov.
他需要这笔保险赔偿金来偿还曼伦科夫
You didn't help us out by escaping，you know.
你逃跑可没给我们帮上什么忙
He figured，
他想通了
what better way to get rid of Malankov and keep the insurance money…
想要得到这笔保险赔偿金 并且摆脱曼伦科夫
than by getting me
最好的计划就是
to kill the guy who would kill him…
让我去杀了那个会去杀他的人
because it was the only way to keep my daughter safe.
因为只有这样才能保证我女儿的安全
Almost worked.
他差点就得逞了
Almost.
差点
So，are we done，Inspector？
那么 督察 我们谈完了吗
Of course.
当然
Of course we're done.
我们谈完了
We're done.
Could you… just stay in town for the next month or so…
你 呃 能不能接下来一个月别出城
just in case I have any other questions for you？
我有可能还有其他的问题要问你
Sure.
当然可以
（犯罪调查）
（布莱恩·米尔斯）
Now，you two.
现在你们两个…
I've thought about this all night.
我一晚上都在想这件事
It's a very important choice.
是一个很重要的选择
Whatever you decide…
不管你们怎么决定
the two of you，together…
你们两个人 一起
I'll support you 100%.
我都会全力支持你们
And I know your mom would have said the same thing，too.
我知道你妈妈也会这么说
- Tell him。- Dad…
- 告诉他吧 - 爸爸
we've been talking.
我们谈过很久了
We thought that…
我们觉得
if it's a girl…
如果是一个女孩
we'd like to name her after mom.
我们想给她取妈妈的名字
She'd like that very much，Kim.
她会很高兴的 金姆